Unified Year 1923, Imperial Army Northern Garrison
It was a few days after the wounds
from my first battle had healed.
（ターニャ）それは―
初戦闘での傷が癒えた
数日後のことだった
Military Commander's Office
Second Lieutenant Degurechaff,
here are your deployment orders.
（軍司令）
デグレチャフ少尉
配属の内示だ
（ターニャ）
拝見いたします
Thank you.
Just don't send me to the front lines...
（ターニャ）前線への配置だけは
勘弁してもらいたいが…
The Tactical Instructor Squad back home?
（ターニャ）
本国の戦技教導隊？
（軍司令）うむ… その年で
部隊教育を任されるとは―
Only someone accomplished
enough to earn the Silver Wings
could be assigned to an instruction
unit at your age.
さすが 銀翼章持ちの
エースだな
That's exactly what I wanted!
（ターニャ）
ま～さに 理想的な配属先！
But I can't make my happiness too obvious.
だが 大げさに喜ぶわけにも
いくまい
This is an honor, but...
（ターニャ）
お言葉は ありがたいですが…
You are dissatisfied?
（軍司令）不満か？
If you have a problem with it,
I can pass it on.
異議があるなら
こちらから申し立てることも…
そんな！ 光栄極まりない評価に
感謝しております
No!
I am grateful for this incredible honor.
But this is a position at the rear,
where it could be said not much is done.
ただ 後方のお飾りと
言えなくもない配属先なので…
Don't worry about it.
気にするな
Even if you are an ace,
deploying you to the front lines
いくらエースとはいえ
その年齢で前線は
対外的にも よろしくないのだろう
would be bad for appearances.
I guess that settles it, then.
ならば しかたないですね
配属命令を受領いたします
Deployment orders received.
This is wonderful!
（ターニャ）
はあ～ 実にワンダフル
すばらしきかな！
安全な後方勤務
Safe, rear-echelon deployments...
How I love you!
Very well.
（軍司令）よろしい
Then head to the General Supply Staff.
では 取り急ぎ
兵站(へいたん)総監部に出向してくれ
Is this for technology testing?
総監部というと
技術検証要員でしょうか？
Yes, they need you to test
a new type of computation jewel.
ああ 新型演算宝珠の
テストらしい
It's true that testing new equipment falls
under the instruction unit's duties...
（ターニャ）確かに―
装備の運用研究も
教導隊の仕事ではある
May I ask about this new jewel?
その新型について お伺いすることは
できますでしょうか？
Unfortunately, all I've been
told that it's a prototype.
残念だが
試作機としか知らされておらん
I understand.
分かりました
ありがとうございまし…
Thank you...
...kidding me?!
You can't be serious!
ふざけるな！
How is this a safe, rear-echelon deployment?!
これのどこが
安全な後方勤務だー！
Cruscos Army Aerial Unit Testing Grounds
Second Lieutenant Degurechaff,
are you conscious?
（助手）
デグレチャフ少尉
意識はありますか？
少尉！
Second Lieutenant!
（ターニャ）
酸素濃度と体温が急激に低下
Oxygen density and body
temperature are dropping fast.
At this rate, I won't last long.
このままでは 長くはもたない
Episode Three
Deus Vult
Elenium Type-95?
（ターニャ）
エレニウム九五式？
（助手）４機の演算宝珠核を
同調させることで
By synchronizing four computation jewel cores,
this prototype grants revolutionary abilities.
革新的な性能を目指す
試作機です
魔力消費量は激しいですが―
It uses tremendous magical energy,
but with the amount you have,
that shouldn't be a problem.
デグレチャフ少尉の魔力量ならば
何も問題は…
There are all kinds of problems!
（ターニャ）ありまくりだ！
（ターニャ）
宝珠の安定性が乏しすぎだ！
These crystals aren't stable at all.
If this keeps up, they'll explode again!
このままでは また爆発する！
Roger.
了解 今回の実験はこれで…
We'll bring this experiment to an—
（シューゲル）ふんっ！
（シューゲル）少尉！
もっと高度は取れんのかね？
Second Lieutenant! Can't you go any higher?!
Doctor?!
ドクトル!?
Theoretically, you should be able
to reach 18,000 meters!
理論上は―
Imperial Military Technology
Development Chief Engineer Adelheid von Schugel
高度１万８０００までの
上昇が確実なはずだ
A standard computation jewel's
maximum altitude is 6,000!
（ターニャ）従来の宝珠の
限界高度は6,000ですよ
The load is within acceptable parameters!
宝珠の負荷は許容値内だ！
Those are theoretical numbers!
それは理論上の話です！
For use as military-grade items,
keep durability in mind!
軍用品としての耐久性を
考慮いただかねば！
何を言っている？
What are you talking about?
最適化された宝珠の同調を
崩す気か！
That would ruin the jewel's
optimized synchronization!
I don't know when this
defective junk will explode!
この欠陥品は いつ 火を噴くか
分からないんですよ！
Defective junk?
欠陥品!?
You called my masterpiece "defective junk"?
私の最高傑作に欠陥品だと？
直ちに発言を取り消したまえ！
Take that back now!
Even if the Empire is a meritocracy,
（ターニャ）いくら帝国が
能力主義とはいえ―
what's a guy like him doing
as a chief engineer?!
こんな男が主任技師とは…
（助手）
ほ… 宝珠核の温度が急上昇！
T-Temperature of jewel cores is rising.
I'm cutting the magic supply
魔力供給をカット
宝珠内の魔力を緊急排出する！
and emergency purging
the jewel's magical energy!
Engine has shut down.
（助手）機関部沈静 動力消失
Motive power lost.
ハァ 前回のような惨事は何とか…
At least there won't be a
disaster like last time...
I am done with this crap!
（ターニャ）もう やってられん！
こんな宝珠―
This thing's as defective as
an Italian Red Devil!
イタリアの“赤い悪魔”並みに
不良品だ！
Second Lieutenant Degurechaff...
デグレチャフ少尉 またかね？
またなのかね？
Again? We're doing this again?!
That's my question.
私こそ“またか”と
言いたいのですが？
セーフティーが
機能しなければ
If the safety hadn't worked, pieces of me
would be raining down on the base!
ミンチになって
散らばっていましたよ！
Wait!
待て！ 報告書は？
Where's your report?
あとにしてください
医務室が先です
Talk to me about it later.
I'm going to the medical room.
It's because you're failing to
concentrate hard enough.
（シューゲル）
君が集中力を欠くからだろう？
それでも軍人かね？
And you call yourself a soldier?
A soldier's job is to use weapons,
（ターニャ）軍人の職責は
兵器を扱うことで―
欠陥品のご機嫌取りでは
ありません！
not spend her time trying to
get defective junk to work!
ま… また 欠陥と言ったな？
Y-You called it "defective junk" again?
（シューゲル）言ったな？
（助手）え… ええ
Didn't she?
Y-Yes.
（シューゲル）取り消したまえ！
Take that back...
前回のとあわせて
取り消したまえ！
For this time and the last time, too!
（ターニャ）
構造が もろすぎるんですよ！
The thing's way too fragile.
こんなもの
観賞用が いいとこです
It'd be more at home in an art museum!
なぜだ？
Why?!
Why don't you understand how revolutionary
the four-way synchronization is?
４機同調が どれほど革新的か
なぜ 理解しない？
（ターニャ）
革新的なのは認めますとも
I'll admit that it's revolutionary.
ですから まともに動くものを
作っていただきたい！
That's why I want you to make
something that works!
理論上は動くのだ！
Theoretically, it works!
So why can't you get it work properly?
君こそ どうして
まともに動かせない？
They say a thin line separates
genius and madness.
（ターニャ）天才とマッドは
紙一重というが―
But I didn't think talking to him
would be impossible.
対話すら成立しないとは…
ドクトル 不都合を生じる
可能性があるものは
Doctor, anything that can
go wrong, will go wrong.
いつか必ず 不都合を生じます
有名な法則でしょう？
That's a famous law.
That's idiotic!
くだらん！
誰が そんな戯言(たわごと)を！
Who said something so stupid?!
If you live a long life, you'll understand!
長生きすれば 分かりますよ！
With the way this is going, I'm doomed!
（ターニャ）このままじゃ
命がいくつあっても足りん！
I'm better off on the damn front lines!
最前線のほうが まだマシだ！
"Request for Transfer"
Imperial Military General Supply Staff, Technology HQ
So, what do we do?
（局員）で どうする？
Do we accept it?
（局員）受理するのかね？
（局員）ハァ… 実は
私にも同じ年頃の娘がいてね
I actually have a daughter about her age.
（局員たち）うむ…
"The brass have decided that the Type-95 is
unreliable and unsuitable for general use.
（ターニャ）上層部は―
九五式が汎用(はんよう)性と信頼性に
欠けると判断
Additional funding has been frozen,
and the project has been, de facto, canceled."
追加予算は凍結され
事実上の打ち切り
Yeah, nothing beats being proactive.
（ターニャ）やはり
主体的な行動あるのみだな
Only incompetents cling to the metaphysical.
形而上の存在に すがるなど―
所詮は 無能のやることだ
In a few days, I'll be on the fast track
in the Imperial capital, coffee in hand.
数日後には 帝都でコーヒー片手に
出世コースか？
This is a serious problem.
（存在Ｘ(エックス)）ゆゆしき事態だな
You haven't developed even
the tiniest bit of faith.
いまだ 信仰のかけらも
芽生えないとは…
B-Being X...
そ… 存在Ｘ!?
Indeed.
（存在Ｘ）いかにも
ハッ！ これほど
うれしくない再会も珍しい
It's rare to have such an unpleasant reunion.
10年たっても
理不尽さに変わりないとは…
Ten years have passed,
and you're still just as unreasonable.
（存在Ｘ）貴様こそ
まるで進歩がないようだ
It seems you've not grown at all, either.
あいにく 神とやらにすがるほど
追い詰められてはいないので
Unfortunately, I'm not desperate
enough to rely on "God."
Your attitude is as unacceptable as ever.
（存在Ｘ）
相変わらず目に余る態度だ
I'd intended to limit my
interference to a minimum,
（存在Ｘ）なるべく
無干渉を貫くつもりだったが―
but foolish little lambs need
to be shown the way.
愚かな子羊には
道を示してやらねばならん
Don't worry about me...
（ターニャ）お気遣いなく
I'm not the type to stay fenced in.
柵の中で飼われるのは
性に合わない
Why will you not praise the Creator?
（存在Ｘ）
なぜ 創造主をたたえん？
Long ago, merely speaking to them
sufficed to make humans worship God.
昔は 語りかけるだけで
人々は神をあがめ―
Sometimes, humanity even called to me.
時には人間側からの
呼びかけすらあった
And so, I should pray to some
traditionally hand-crafted knick-knack?
だから伝統工芸品にも
祈りを捧げろと？
You're kidding me.
ご冗談でしょ？
Perhaps I should give you a blessing.
（存在Ｘ）やはり 恩寵(おんちょう)を
与えるべきなのかもしれんな
A blessing?
恩寵？
A miracle.
（存在Ｘ）奇跡だ
Gonna part the seas or something?
海でも割ってみるおつもりですか？
Or change water into wine?
それとも
水をワインに変えてみます？
Miracles are illusions caused by
insufficient observation and understanding.
奇跡など
観測と体系化が不十分ゆえの錯覚
They're just...
言うなれば…
glorious misunderstandings.
すばらしき勘違いです
I don't know about that.
（存在Ｘ）果たして
そう言い切れるかな？
夢？
A dream?
"Deus lo vult."
“Deus(デウス) lo(ロ) vult(ウルト)”
"God wills it"?
“神がそれを望まれる”？
Can we seriously not?
（ターニャ）
本気でやめませんか？
An experiment with magical-energy
多重干渉誘発による
魔力変換固定化検証
transformation and affixation,
via multilayer interference.
Since the project's canceled,
どのみち開発中止なら―
I'll obviously do the experiments
I'd been putting off, right?
見送っていた試験をやるのが
当然だろう
If you fail, it could blow up
the whole proving grounds.
失敗すれば 試験場ごと
吹っ飛びかねませんが…
The march of progress always has victims.
（シューゲル）
科学の進歩に犠牲は付き物だよ
Of course, it won't be only you.
I won't move from this spot.
もちろん 君だけではなく
私も ここを動かない
正直 その熱意を別のベクトルに
向けていただきたいのですが…
To be honest, I'd prefer if you found
another use for your passion.
A scientist must be loyal
to his research, right?
科学者たるもの
探究に忠実であるべきだろう？
私は科学者ではなく 軍人です
I'm a soldier, not a scientist.
Then I should give you an order.
では 命令せざるをえないな
少尉 準備はいいかね？
Lieutenant, are you ready?
Observation teams standing by.
（助手）観測班 スタンバイ
Activating energy supply to the Type-95.
九五式への魔力供給を開始します
Guess I'm out of ideas now...
（ターニャ）
もはや 万策尽きたか…
Second Lieutenant Tanya
Degurechaff, taking off!
ターニャ･デグレチャフ少尉
進発します！
Present altitude 4,000 meters.
現在 高度4,000
速度320で上昇中
Climbing at a speed of 320.
ううっ… うおっと！
The jewel's synchronization is unstable.
宝珠の同調が不安定
このままでは暴走確実！
It's going to explode!
Lieutenant,
（シューゲル）少尉
心配は要らない
no need to worry.
既に 成功は
約束されたようなものだ
Our success is assured.
Doctor...
（ターニャ）ドクトル？
どこから そんな自信が
Where are you getting that confidence?
（シューゲル）
なに 簡単なことだったんだよ
It's simple.
Last night, I received divine inspiration.
私は昨夜 天啓を得てね
I heard God's voice, and an idea came
to me by divine inspiration.
天意のアイデアと共に―
神の声を聞いた
The god of inventions revealed himself.
発明の神が舞い降りたのだ
Doctor, I thought you were an atheist.
ドクトル あなたは
無神論者だったはずでは？
今や敬けんな信徒だよ
I'm a devout believer now.
Haven't you also met God, Lieutenant?
少尉 君も
神に会ったことがあるのだろう？
If we pray to God, he will grant our wishes!
我らが神に祈れば
必ずや願いは かなう！
Otherwise, we both become martyrs here!
でなければ ２人して殉教だ！
魔力係数に異変！ 暴走です！
Irregularity in energy coefficients.
They're going out of control.
I'm purging the magical energy.
魔力を緊急排出する！
No!
（助手）ダメです！
同調が乱れて宝珠ごと崩壊します
That will disrupt synchronization
and destroy the jewel!
クソッ！ 安全装置を…
Damn it!
The safety...
It's not working?
起動しない まさか…
Is this...
This is a good opportunity, right?
いい機会であろう
共に神へ祈ろうではないか！
Let us both pray to God!
Jewel cores on the verge of fusion!
宝珠核が融解寸前！
You got me...
謀ったな… 謀ったな 存在Ｘ！
You set me up, Being X!
I have blessed your computation jewel
（存在Ｘ）貴様の演算宝珠を祝福し
奇跡を成した
and performed a miracle.
A miracle?
奇跡？ 爆弾を突きつけるのが
奇跡だと？
You call strapping a bomb to me a miracle?!
Now, you must pray to God
（存在Ｘ）今後 貴様は
宝珠を使うたび―
each time you use your computation jewel.
神への祈りを
唱えずにはいられない
And eventually, your heart
will be filled with faith.
（存在Ｘ）やがて 貴様の心も
信仰に満たされるであろう
Th-That's cheating.
あ… 悪質すぎるマッチポンプ！
どこまでクソッタレなんだ！
You vile piece of shit!
Go now,
（存在Ｘ）さあ 行くがよい
and spread the name of God.
主の御名(みな)を広めるために！
God's miracles are great.
神の奇跡は偉大なり
Praise the Lord
主をたたえよ
and his worthy name.
その誉れ高き名を…
What did I...
はっ… 私は何を？
Did I just pray?
まさか 祈りを捧げた？
あれに？
To that thing?!
The cores' synchronization stabilized.
４機同調が安定
空間座標への魔力固定化に成功
Magical energy successfully affixed
to spatial coordinates!
I never thought it would actually work.
（観測係）
まさか 本当に成功するとは…
（ターニャ）これは確かに
性能だけ見れば すばらしい
If you just look at the results,
this thing is amazing...
It's amazing,
すばらしいが 呪われている！
but it's cursed!
We did it! We did it!
It worked!
I knew it... God is real.
やはり 主はおられた
Deus lo vult...
“デウス･ロ･ウルト”
神がそれを望まれるのだ
God wills it.
Unified Year 1924, Rhine Theater
I praise the power of the Lord
我 主の御力(みちから)をたたえ
その お恵みに感謝せん
and give thanks for his blessings.
First, that unreasonable reincarnation,
（ターニャ）理不尽な転生のあげく
こんな呪いまで…
and now this curse.
But I have to use it to survive
on the front lines...
だが 前線で生き残るためには
使わざるをえない
What a dilemma.
何というジレンマ…
（ヴィーシャ）しょ… 少尉
何か気になることでも？
L-Lieutenant, is there a problem?
No!
ない 仕事に集中しろ
Focus on your work.
は… はい！
R-Right.
But the main unit from
the nation's center has gathered.
ですが 中央本隊は集結済みですし
これ以上の増援は必要ないかと…
I don't know if we need
further reinforcements.
何だと？
What did you say?
ひっ！ し… 失礼しました！
I-I'm sorry!
I'm on the front lines with a cursed jewel...
（ターニャ）
最前線に呪われた宝珠とは…
存在Ｘに災いあれ！
Curse you, Being X!
Imperial Strategic Headquarters Strategy and Operations Bureau
As the documents you see state...
（レルゲン）お手元の
資料にあるように―
After Second Lieutenant Degurechaff's
first battle with the Entente Alliance,
デグレチャフ少尉は―
協商連合軍との初陣後に
銀翼突撃章を受賞
she received the Silver Wings Assault Badge.
After contributing to development
of a new computation jewel,
新型宝珠の開発に尽力した後
changes in the military situation led to her
emergency deployment to the Rhine theater.
戦局の変化により
ライン戦線へ緊急配備されました
（ルーデルドルフ）ライン戦線では
単独で敵魔導中隊を殲滅(せんめつ)
While in the Rhine theater, she wiped out
an entire enemy mage company on her own...
And she's still carrying out
assault missions there?
現在も同地にて
よう撃任務を継続中か…
She's the ideal soldier.
まさに理想的な軍人だな
Why do you call her a monster?
こんな逸材を
なぜ“化物”と？
I won't deny that she is a talented mage.
確かに優秀な魔導師であることは
間違いありません
But her personality is extremely unusual.
しかし その人格は
極めて異質です
（ルーデルドルフ）
士官学校での話か？
Is this about the training school incident?
跳ねっ返りを たたくのも
上官の務めだろう
Keeping rebellious new recruits in line
is part of an officer's job.
She is the only one presently capable
of using that computation jewel.
現状 新型宝珠は 少尉以外に
使いこなせないそうです
I believe that indicates latent danger, too.
その点からも潜在的に
危惧せざるえない存在かと…
You aren't mistaken, Lieutenant Colonel?
（准将）中佐の誤解じゃないのか？
（准将）まだ10歳じゃないか
She's still ten.
She's just a kid.
（准将）ただの子供だ
Lieutenant Colonel Rerugen,
（ゼートゥーア）レルゲン中佐
I'm told that you are very good at your job.
貴官が優れた人材であることは
聞き及んでいる
Your transfer from Personnel to
Operations was, in part,
人事局から作戦局への異動も
その幅広い知識を見込んでのものだ
due to your wide range of knowledge.
You overestimate me, but thank you.
過分な評価 感謝しております
（ゼートゥーア）
そんな貴官が進言する以上―
And because of that,
I want to respect your opinion
as much as possible, but...
可能なかぎり
意見は尊重したいが…
We have already decided what to do
with Second Lieutenant Degurechaff!
既にデグレチャフ少尉の処遇は
決定済みだ
（ヴィーシャ）
あ～ フカフカのベッドで寝たい
I want to sleep in a comfy bed.
シャワー 浴びたい
I want to take a shower.
缶詰でもいいから
アップルパイ 食べたい
I want to eat apple pie,
even if it's from a can...
J-Just kidding!
ウ… ウソです！
I have no dissatisfaction with our mission!
任務に不満など
少しもありません！
数か月前は ろくに
飛べもしなかった新入りが
Just a few months ago, you were so
new to this, you could barely fly.
And now look at you.
随分 慣れたものだな
This isn't good.
（ヴィーシャ）マズい…
I hope I don't end up like Kurst and Harald...
まさか クルストたちみたいに
私も…
（ターニャ）シュワルコフ中尉に
取り次いでもらい―
I spoke to Lieutenant Schwarzkopf and
recommended you for an officer track.
将校課程に推薦しておいた
I'm going to be an officer?
（ヴィーシャ）私が将校に？
If you don't want to leave the muddy
and bloody front lines, I won't force you.
泥と血にまみれた前線を
離れたくないなら
無理にとは言わんが…
No, no, no, no, no!
い… いえいえいえ…
そうではなくて
That's not it!
It just seems too good to be true.
うれしすぎるというか
身に余る評価に
混乱しているというか…
I'm not sure how to handle it...
Head back to the capital
as soon as you're ready.
（ターニャ）
支度が整いしだい 帝都へ戻れ
Lieutenant, um...
少尉！ あの…
What?
何だ？
（ヴィーシャ）その配属先
砲弾で吹っ飛んだりしませんよね？
My new deployment area won't
be blown up by artillery, right?
ハァ…
God is real, huh?
神様っているんだな
"Second Lieutenant Degurechaff,
you are hereby promoted to First Lieutenant
（ターニャ）
“ターニャ･デグレチャフ少尉”
“貴官は中尉に昇進
軍大学へ入学すべし”
and are to attend the military academy."
This is the second time I can remember
that I've been to university...
（ターニャ）
主観記憶にあるかぎり―
２度目の大学生活か～
I'll get a nice easy job studying at the rear!
まさか 後方で
安全に学問ができるとは…
Looks like your ride isn't here yet.
（シュワルコフ）
まだ 迎えは来ないようだな
Lieutenant Schwarzkopf!
シュワルコフ中尉殿！
You're always so cold.
You won't even let me see you off?
（シュワルコフ）
相変わらず つれないヤツだ
見送りもさせてくれないとは
（ターニャ）申し訳ありません
I'm sorry.
部隊を離れて帝都に戻るのは
気が引けまして…
I didn't feel right about leaving
the unit and returning to the capital.
Is that why you recommended
Corporal Serebryakov for officer training?
セレブリャコーフ伍長(ごちょう)を
将校課程に推薦したのも
それが理由か？
She worked directly under me, after all.
直属の部下ですからね
She's already left.
彼女は 一足先に
出発したそうです
And this makes me look like a superior
officer who cares for her troops.
（ターニャ）これで部下を配慮する
軍人としてのポーズにも―
抜かりはない
I want to thank you again.
改めて 貴官に礼を言いたい
その働きぶりと新型宝珠には
本当に助けられた
Your hard work and new computation jewel have really helped us.
こちらこそ
中尉殿には感謝しております
No, thank you, Lieutenant.
Unfortunately, I won't have much chance
to use this thing at the academy.
残念ながら 大学では
これを使う機会も減るでしょうが…
Either way, I wish you luck.
（シュワルコフ）何はともあれ
貴官の武運を祈ろう
God is always with us.
神は常に我らと共に
わ… 我ら… と共に！
W-With u-us!
What's the situation in the Rhine theater?
（ゼートゥーア）
現在のライン戦線の状況は？
Still a stalemate.
（ルーデルドルフ）
依然として膠着(こうちゃく)状態だ
どうにか
中央本隊は間に合ったが―
The main unit made it there.
But our pre-war plans are proving useless.
やはり 戦前の想定計画では
話にならん
So our main force is lacking
in mobility and adaptability?
肝心の主力が 機動性と適合性を
欠いているというわけか…
Our current task is to establish a powerful
unit that can adapt to any situation.
（ルーデルドルフ）
状況に即応できる
精強な部隊の設立が―
当面の課題だな
（ゼートゥーア）ハァ…
Warm food and an easy life
await me in the capital...
（ターニャ）帝都で待つのは
温かな食事と快適な生活
If I can get on the rails
at the military academy,
軍大学で出世のレールに乗れば
将来は確約される
my future is as good as made.
A new rapid-response unit, huh?
（ゼートゥーア）
新たな即応部隊か…
I was worried for a while.
（ターニャ）
一時は どうなるかと思ったが…
But now I feel kind of bad for Being X.
今や 存在Ｘが哀れなほどだ
A farewell gift?
（ターニャ）餞別(せんべつ)？
（ヴィーシャ）あっ はい
Y-Yes, you've done so much for me.
小隊長には
お世話になりっぱなしでしたし―
And so, I wanted to thank you.
せめて何か
お礼をと思いまして
Looking at it, it's obvious that it won't fit.
見るからに
各部の寸法が合わないと思うが？
そうですか？
It won't?
But you're a growing girl.
でも 小隊長は育ち盛りですし
すぐに合うようになりますよ！
It'll fit you soon!
This program is fiction.
All persons, groups, places, laws,
and names appearing in it have
no relation to the real world.
Next Episode
Campus Life